Demid Strukov

Game Developer

Ukraine

3 27 July 1998

+38 (099) 089 55 95

https://github.com/CrishNate

https://gitlab.com/CrishNate

demidemid1@gmail.com

@crishnate

https://www.linkedin.com/in/demi d-strukov-45887317b

https://crishnate.github.io/portfolio

Personal

A skilled game developer with over 5 years of experience, that is enjoy creating games as much as playing them. Focused on in-game Al systems. Communicative and ready to seek new opportunities in education and self-improvement. Passionate about helping people and mentoring them.

Skills

Programming Languages

• C/C++

• C#

Python

Lua

Tools & Technologies

• Unreal 4/5

Unity

• GAS

• VS / Rider

 VSC (Git, Perforce) • PIX

Dlamalan 70

• Blender 3D

Photoshop

Fields

Gameplay

• Al / Al Design

OptimizationTools

• Shader

User Interface

Animation

AR / VR

• 3D modeling

Multiplayer

Languages

English Intermediate B2

Russian *Native*Ukrainian *Native*

Employment

Al Programmer – 4A Games Ukraine

Feb. 2022 - present

- Develop AI and Core systems aimed to improve interaction between player and NPCs.
- Collaborated with the design team to ensure game design and feature requirements were met.
- Researched and developed tools to improve development efficiency within the project.

Unreal Developer 5 - Encore

Apr. 2022 - Dec. 2022

- Metaverse runner game based on combining NFT and Action multiplayer game.
- Refactor of existing code base. Improving animation management system.
- Refactor of game UI.
- Testing and optimizing app build.
- Creating an AI bot, that behaves like a player.

Unreal Developer 4 / Unity - Monolith Mind

Feb. 2021 - March. 2022

- Developing of CCG type game.
- Implementing and management of game logic, mostly related to UI.
- Debugging and fixing bugs. Improving overall experience of the game.

Unreal Developer 4 - Rogue Arts

Dec. 2018 - Sept. 2020

- Action multiplayer battle royal game.
- Develop, implement & improve new gameplay features.
- Ensure that everything is working correctly in multiplayer.
- Writing clean C++ code.

Certificates

CCNA Routing and Switching: Introduction to

Networks

ID 2019-2046

Education

The National Technical University of Ukraine "Igor Sikorsky Kyiv Polytechnic Institute"

Radio Technician - Master

2021 - 2023

Radio Technician - Bachelor

2018 - 2021